let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which spell is used to  'Create a Loud Sound' ?",
    answer: "Caterwauling Charm",
    options: [
      "Expulso",
      "Caterwauling Charm",
      "Impervius",
      "Diffindo"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which spell is used to 'Summon Objects Towards Caster'?",
    answer: "Accio",
    options: [
      "Priori Incantato",
      "Stupefy",
      "Accio",
      "Locomoior"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which spell is used to 'Make Objects Smaller'?",
    answer: "Reducio",
    options: [
      "Reducio",
      "Diffindo",
      "Oppugno",
      "Morsmordre"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which spell is used to ' Duplicate An Object'?",
    answer: "Geminio",
    options: [
      "Homenum Revelio",
      "Geminio",
      "Incendio",
      "Langlock"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which spell is used to 'Produce Fire'?",
    answer: "Incendio",
    options: [
      "Fidelius",
      "Incendio",
      "Flagrate",
      "Muffliato"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which spell is used to 'Manipulate An Object'?",
    answer: "Wingardium Leviosa",
    options: [
      "Evanesco",
      "Wingardium Leviosa",
      "Duro",
      "Sectumsempra"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which spell is used to 'Cause The Victim Intense Pain'?",
    answer: "Crucio",
    options: [
      "Crucio",
      "Defodio",
      "Orchideous",
      "Petrificus"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which spell is used to 'Turn A Wand Into A Snake '?",
    answer: "Serpensortia",
    options: [
      "Serpensortia",
      "Specialis Revelio",
      "Homenum Revelio",
      "Levicorpus"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which spell is used to 'Mend Broken Objects'?",
    answer: "Reparo",
    options: [
      "Colloporus",
      "Wingardium Leviosa",
      "Reparo",
      "Riddikuls"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which spell is used to 'Unlock And Open Doors'? ",
    answer: "Alohomora",
    options: [
      "Geminio",
      "Alohomora",
      "Episkey",
      "Expecio Patronum"
   ]
  },
];